askandyaboutclothes.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Ask Andy About Clothes

### Introduction

At AskAndyAboutClothes.com the privacy and security of our customers and visitors are of paramount importance. This privacy policy explains how we process information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify an individual (“Personal Data”) collected through use of our website.

All information is stored securely and is accessed by authorized personnel only with information hosted and operated in Quebec, Canada.  Additional  development, support and maintenance operations are in the United States.

We implement and maintain appropriate technical, security and organizational measures to protect Personal Data against unauthorized or unlawful processing and use, and against accidental loss, destruction, damage, theft or disclosure.

### What information do we collect?

Each time you visit our website Personal Data is collected. That information is specific to your visit. Depending your actions, different and unique information is gathered.

We will only collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, or place an order. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address, country, state, zip code and city. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

AskAndyAboutClothes.com is proud to inform you that we do not sell or share your Personal Data or email. Your information is only used to complete your order and provide updates to you. Should you select the optional opportunity to receive promotional emails from us about current offers and incentives, we will also use your email for this purpose. If you have not selected this Opt-in option, you will not receive promotional emails. If you have opted to receive promotional emails, or if you receive transactional emails about your incomplete order, you may choose to remove (Opt-out) this feature at any time and the emails will be stopped.

Additionally, your contact information may be used should we ever need to contact you regarding your order. Gift certificates and gifts also require that information be shipped to third parties. This information receives the same courtesy detailed above for our customers.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email footer.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Data when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your Personal Data. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the  
information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and keep track of advertisements.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Data. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based  
advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at:  
http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

### **Processing in the European Economic Area (EEA)**

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) related to your Personal Data.   All processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and our processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR.

Furthermore, we process Personal Data both as a Processor and as a Controller, as defined in the Directive and the GDPR.

Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, every customer shall have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of his or her habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if the customer considers that the processing of personal data relating to him or her infringes this Regulation.

You may contact us at any time to:

  * Request access to information that we have about you
  * Correct or make an objection to any information that we have about you
  * Delete any or all information that we have about you

Any data that is no longer needed for the purposes specified will be deleted. If you have any additional questions about our collection and storage of data, please contact us at: [data@askandyaboutclothes.com](mailto:data@askandyaboutclothes.com).

#### AdThrive: For European Economic Area Residents

As mentioned in the above section, if you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at the email above and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your Personal Data to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By visiting this website, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data as described. Kindly note that any consent will be entirely voluntary. However, if you do not grant the requested consent to the processing of your Personal Data, some features of our website may not be possible, such as participating in our forums.

Your Personal Data is retained in perpetuity, unless you withdraw consent. Consent may be withdrawn at any time by emailing us at [data@askandyaboutclothes.com](mailto:data@askandyaboutclothes.com).

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to update or make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes accordingly here: askandyaboutclothes.com/privacy-policy
